Neufeld, Maurice Papers /3007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. CORRESPONDENCE/ADMINISTRATIVE FILES
  - Committees - ILR - Extension - I, 1961-1971 (Box 5, Folder 17-20)
    "The Mission of Extension" [11/17/71], draft of Doherty's Report to the Dean on Labor/Liberal Arts Program [7/2/71], income statement of Labor/Liberal Arts Program for 4/1/70-3/31/71, "Background and Evolution of Cornell's ILR School Two-Year Labor-Liberal Arts Program" (w/ other program info), memo from Risley to program students re program and establishment of an associate degree program [6/18/71],
  - Committees - ILR - Extension - II, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 21-26)
  - Committees - ILR - Graduate, 1946-1950 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    "Graduate Work in Industrial and Labor Relations" [2/9/49], "The Present Organization and Operating Procedures of the Graduate Program in ILR".
  - Committees - ILR - Graduate, 1951-1953 (Box 5, Folder 28-30)
    "Report of Investigation and Appraisal of Graduate Work in NYSSILR with Suggestions and Recommendations for Improvement" [2/11/53], motion presented by MFN to faculty meeting re commissioning an appraisal of graduate work [1/11/52].
  - Committees - ILR - Graduate, 1954-1967 (Box 5, Folder 31-33)
    Minutes of meetings (including 6/2/67 election of Prof. Evans as chairman, 7/26/66 election of John Windmuller as chairman), "Statement of Possible Changes in MILR Degree Requirements" re including Labor Law as a requirement, "Proposed Change in the Standards and Practices of the Graduate Field of ILR Concerning the Composition of the Special Committee" re procedures for grad students with one major and one minor [10/11/66], "Major and Minor Fields of Study-Doctoral Candidates" [9/7/66], memo from committee to graduate faculty re problems with and suggestions for graduate work [11/12/62].
  - Committees - ILR - Graduate, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34-37)
    Memo from committee to faculty re proposal for MILR-LL.B. program [10/10/69], minutes of meetings (including 5/22/68 election of MFN to chairman), "Handbook of Policies and Practices for Graduate Students in the Field of ILR" [4/21/69], memo from committee to graduate faculty re proposed changes in MILR curriculum [1/9/68], memo from Graduate Student Council to MFN re majority of students' unwillingness to strike [3/19/69], memo from John Windmuller to committee re recruitment and admissions of disadvantaged students [1/21/69].
  - Committees - ILR - Graduate, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Committees - ILR - International Affairs, 1959-1964 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    Minutes of meetings. Memo from Prof. Raimon to Prof. Clark, Donovan, Mcconnell, MFN, and John Windmuller re possible focus of international program [11/15/61], routine correspondence
  - Committees - ILR - Nominations and Elections, 1956-1977 (Box 5, Folder 40-42)
  - Committees - ILR - Personnel Policy, 1959-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1-6)
    Faculty grievance procedure, memo from MFN to Prof. Dyer re suggestions for changes in faculty personnel guidelines and practices [5/14/75], memo re proposed amendment to "Summary of Present Practice and Recommendations Concerning ILR Faculty Personnel Policy" [5/8/67], minutes of meetings (discussion of the impression that the school was becoming a human relations institution and how to rectify that [1/22/64]), "Faculty Legislation" [1/63].
  - Committees - ILR - Placement, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Minutes of meetings, memo from Martin P. Catherwood to Hanson re formation of committee [9/22/49].
  - Committees - ILR - Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 8-12)
    "Final Report of the Planning Committee on the Mission of the ILR School" [12/71].
  - Committees - ILR - Planning, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    1976-77 Budget, minutes of meeting [11/10/76], draft of 1977- 80 Long Range Plan [5/13/75].
  - Committees - ILR - Research and Publications, 1948-1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Minutes of meetings (MFN elected chairman for 1957-58 [9/13/57]), "Freedom and Responsibility for Research" [10/2/53].
  - Committees - ILR - Scholarships and Awards, 1946-1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Nominations for Daniel J. Alpern Memorial Prizes (Gary Bettman, NHL Commissioner, nominated [5/1/74], Douglas Ginsburg, Judge, U.S. Court of Appeals, D.C. Cir.; withdrawn nominee for U.S. Supreme Court, nominated [4/17/70]), minutes of meetings
  - Committees - ILR - Social, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Committees - ILR - Student Activities, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Committees - ILR - Undergraduate Program, 1947-1963 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
    Committee recommendations, proposed curriculum revisions
  - Committees - ILR - Undergraduate Program, 1963-1970 (Box 6, Folder 20-22)
    Committee recommendations, proposed curriculum changes (including MFN's suggestion to reduce the number of required courses [2/15/68]).
  - Committees - ILR - Undergraduate Program, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 23-24)
    Committee recommendations, proposed curriculum revisions, memo from MFN to Aronson re MFN's belief that dropping the two-semester American history requirement "has robbed students of knowledge essential to the intelligent study of ILR" [2/2/73], minutes of meeting [11/3/72].
  - Commons, John R., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Routine correspondence re Lisa Polisar's oral history project on Commons
  - Conferences, Meetings - ILR, 1952-1957 (Box 6, Folder 26-29)
    Schedules, programs, papers, reports.
  - Conferences, Meetings - ILR, 1958-1970 (Box 6, Folder 30-34)
    Schedules, programs, papers. Includes articles.
  - Conferences, Meetings - ILR, 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 35-38)
    Schedules, programs, papers, reports. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Conferences, Meetings - ILR - Foreign Groups and Individuals, 1950-1976 (Box 6, Folder 38-43)
    Schedules, programs, reports. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Conferences, Meetings - Outside, 1948-1971 (Box 6, Folder 44-47)
    Schedules, programs. Includes articles.
  - Conferences, Meetings - Outside, 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Schedules, programs
  - Conferences, Meetings - Outside - Anglo-American Colloquium, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2-5)
    Program, papers (including MFN's "The Realms of Thought and Organized Labor in the Age of Jackson").
  - Cook, Alice H. - Correspondence, 1947-1978 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
    Corres from MFN to Cook re Mcconnell's ("Jack's") decision to accept the presidency at the University of New Hampshire [11/2/62]. Includes articles.
  - Cornell University - Administration, 1946-1966 (Box 7, Folder 8-14)
    "Memorial Convocation Honoring John Fitzgerald Kennedy" [11/23/63], "Inauguration Address of James Alfred Perkins, Seventh President of Cornell University" [10/4/63]. Includes newspaper clippings and articles
  - Cornell University - Administration, 1966-1975 (Box 7, Folder 15-20)
    Routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings and articles.
  - Cornell University - Administration, 1975-1987 (Box 7, Folder 21-27)
  - Cornell University - Administration - Trash Plant, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Newspaper clippings
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Africana Studies and Research Center, 1968-1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Agriculture, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools -Architecture, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Arts and Sciences, 1966-1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Business and Public Administration, 1964-1974 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    routine correspondence
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Graduate School, 1945-1968 (Box 7, Folder 34-38)
    Corres from Dean G. Watts Cunningham to Prof. Bradley re Faculty of graduate School's approval of NYSSILR's M.S. and M.I.L.R. degree programs [2/28/46]. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Graduate School, 1969-1975 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Graduate School General Committee - Language Requirement, 1948-1959 (Box 7, Folder 40-42)
    Memo from Dean Charles W. Jones to MFN and Profs. Guerlac and Kent forming language requirement subcommittee and naming MFN chair [7/9/51].
  - Cornell University - Colleges and Schools - Human Ecology, 1966-1975 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Cornell University - Committees (General and Miscellaneous), 1946-1967 (Box 7, Folder 44-49)
    Corres from MFN to Provost Adams re MFN's acceptance of the chairmanship of the Committee on the Scheduling of Public Events [9/25/47]. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Cornell University - Committees (General and Miscellaneous), 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 50-53)
  - Cornell University - Committees (General and Miscellaneous), 1969-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Academic Problems Arising from Governmental Investigations, 1953-1960 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
    Transcript of Prof. Philip Morrison's testimony before the Senate Internal Security Sub-Committee [5/7/53], minutes of Academic Problems Committee meeting [4/28/53]. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Cornell University - Committees - Advisory Council on University Archives, 1951-1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Arts, 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 7-12)
    Routine correspondence. Includes articles
  - Cornell University - Committees - Arts, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 13-17)
    Routine correspondence. Includes articles.
  - Cornell University - Committees - Arts, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 18-21)
  - Cornell University - Committees Centennial Celebration, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 22-26)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Discrimination Commission, 1958-1964 (Box 8, Folder 27-30)
    Routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings and articles
  - Cornell University - Committees - Faculty Council (Policy), 1955-1970 (Box 8, Folder 31-40)
    University By-Laws [6/13/55].
  - Cornell University - Committees - Forty-One Signers, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Routine correspondence re the Committee of 41, of which the members (all faculty) have agreed not to resign as long as "'essential conditions' of teaching and scholarly work are maintained." Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Cornell University - Committees - Humanities, Society for the, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Humanities Council, 1963-1967 (Box 8, Folder 44-48)
    Telegram from Lawrence F. O'Brien, Special Assistant to the President, to MFN re an invitation for MFN to attend the signing of the bill providing for the establishment of the National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities [9/23/65]. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Cornell University - Committees - Interdisciplinary Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Library Art, 1957-1962 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Library Associates, 1955-1960 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Library Board, 1951-1962 (Box 8, Folder 53-57)
    Corres from MFN to Ives re MFN's request that Ives record his recollections of the founding of the ILR school for archival purposes [1/22/52] and other routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Cornell University - Committees - Land Grant Mission, 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1-7)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Long Range Planning, 1955-1960 (Box 9, Folder 8-14)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Long Range Planning, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 15-20)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Long Range Planning, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 21-25)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Long Range Planning, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 26-31)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Nominations, 1949-1969 (Box 9, Folder 32-35)
  - Cornell University - Committees - President Selection and Retirement, 1962-1969 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Promotions and Appeals Process, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 37-44)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Promotions and Appeals Process, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 45-50)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Science, Technology and Society, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Social Science Research Center, Executive Committee, 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 1-8)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Social Science Research Center, Executive Committee, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 9-14)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Social Science Research Center, Executive Committee, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 14-18)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Social Science Research Center, Executive Committee, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University - Committees Undergraduate Education, 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 20-26)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Urban Development Research, 1963-1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Cornell University - Committees - Women's Studies Program, 1972-1980 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Cornell University - Conferences, Meetings, 1951-1964 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University - Faculty Meetings and Activities, 1949-1956 (Box 10, Folder 30-33)
  - Cornell University - Faculty Meetings and Activities, 1957-1960 (Box 10, Folder 34-38)
  - Cornell University - Faculty Meetings and Activities, 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 39-45)
  - Cornell University - Faculty Meetings and Activities, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 1-7)
  - Cornell University - Faculty Meetings and Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 8-12)
  - Cornell University - Faculty Meetings and Activities, 1971-1980 (Box 11, Folder 13-19)
  - Cornell University - History, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 20-24)
    Routine correspondence. Includes articles. Many of these documents, including MFN's "diary", concern the 1969 Willard Straight Hall takeover.
  - Cornell University - History, 1969-1977 (Box 11, Folder 25-27)
  - Cornell University - History - Clippings, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 28-32)
  - Cornell University - History - Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 33-37)
  - Cornell University - History - Clippings, 1971-1978 (Box 11, Folder 38-39)
  - Cornell University - Libraries, 1964-1981 (Box 11, Folder 40-43)
  - Cornell University - Libraries, 1982-1987 (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
  - Cornell University - Libraries - Felix Reichmann Fund, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University - Libraries - Manuscripts and University Archives Department, Advisory Committee on, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University - Libraries - Olin Library User's Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 7-11)
  - Cornell University - Ombudsman, 1966-1983 (Box 12, Folder 12-14)
  - Cornell University - Oral History Project, 1964-1971 (Box 12, Folder 15-17)
  - Cornell University - Senate, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University - Trustees, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - COSEP, 1971-1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Courses - Cornell - Undergraduate, 1948-1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Courses - Fredonia State Teachers College, 1953-1955 (Box 12, Folder 22-26)
    Syllabi, lecture notes, and routine correspondence. Contains articles, including "Labor Relations and Elementary Teachers" by MFN
  - Courses - ILR - Discontinued - ILR 1, 1945-1950 (Box 12, Folder 27-28)
    Syllabi, lecture notes and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR - Discontinued - ILR 24, ILR 70, ILR 73, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 29-30)
    Syllabi and routine correspondence, including corres from MFN to NLRB officers, among them Chairman Paul M. Herzog, re obtaining materials for ILR 70
  - Courses - ILR - General, 1955-1979 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Course descriptions and schedules and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate, 1946-1979 (Box 12, Folder 32-33)
    Syllabi, course descriptions and schedules, list of requirements for graduate degrees, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 34-38)
    Sept. 1973-Aug. 1975. Proposals for Baruch- Cornell Program for an M.S. in Industrial Relations, memo from Field of ILR to General Committee of the Graduate School re field's approval of the program [5/30/75], and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 39-40)
    Sept. 1975. Memo from Field of ILR to General Committee of the Graduate School re proposal for implementation of M.S. program in NYC [9/29/75] and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
    Oct. 1975- Nov. 1975. Memo from MFN to McKersie re special faculty committee on the master's degree program unanimously approved the program on 10/23/75 [10/28/75], corres from William W. Lambert, Dean of the Graduate School, to MFN re General Committee of the Graduate School's approval of the program [10/21/75], memo from Field of ILR to General Committee of the Graduate School re revised proposal for program [10/15/75], and routine correspondence. Contains newspaper clippings, including Cornell Chronicle article re Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees' approval of the program [11/13/75].
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 6-15)
    Dec. 1975-Mar. 1977. Memo from McKersie to MFN and Calvert re agreement between ILR School and Baruch College on aspects of the program [2/15/77] and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 16-19)
    Apr. 1977-May 1979. Minutes of a meeting of the Faculty Council of Representatives re FCR's unanimous approval of the program [11/9/77], press release re Exec. Committee of the Board of Trustees' 11/9/77 approval of program, scheduled to start in Spring 1978 [11/10/77], Agreement between Cornell and Baruch re program [10/6/77], memo from MFN to McKersie re chronology of events in history of program [9/28/77], Memorandum of Understanding for the program [5/31/77], and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Applications, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City Auxiliary Materials - Budget, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City Auxiliary Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Auxiliary Materials - Course Outlines, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 24-26)
    Course descriptions and outlines.
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Auxiliary Materials - Curriculum Plan, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 27-28)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Auxiliary Materials - Other Programs, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 30-35)
    Baruch Course Descriptions and Faculty Vitae and 4/1/76 Proposal to CUNY.
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - Baruch-Cornell Proposal, Master Copy, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - Committee Meetings and Memos, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - Course Descriptions and Offerings, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 39-40)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - Graduate Committee Report, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - McKersie Packet, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - Miscellaneous Exhibits, Letters, Etc, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - Ferguson, Prof. Robert - NYU & Baruch Meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Courses - ILR - Graduate - New York City - ILR Course Descriptions, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
    Course descriptions and program proposal.
  - Courses - ILR - Student Proposed, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Course proposal and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR - Undergraduate, 1946-1975 (Box 14, Folder 11-14)
    Syllabi, lecture outlines, course proposal, course schedules and descriptions, undergraduate curricula, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Courses - ILR 100 - General, 1968-1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 200, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Fall 1962. Exams, syllabi, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Fall 1969. Routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Tests
  - Courses - ILR 200, 1969-1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Other Sections. Syllabi and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200B, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
    Spring 1976. Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 200C, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 22-24)
    Fall 1970. Syllabi, class handouts, student papers, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200C, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 25-27)
    Fall 1971. Syllabi, class handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200C, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 28-30)
    Fall 1972. Syllabi, class handouts, transparencies, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200C, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    Fall 1973. Syllabi, class handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200C, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 33-36)
    Fall 1975. Syllabi, class handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 200C, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    Tapes and Slides
  - Courses - ILR 200E, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    Fall 1974. Syllabi, class handouts, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Fall 1952. Syllabus and exams
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Fall 1953. Routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
    Fall 1954. Syllabus and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Fall 1955. Routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Fall 1957. Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Fall 1959. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Fall 1961. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 350, 1946-1963 (Box 15, Folder 14-17)
  - Courses - ILR 350, 351 - Cook, Prof. Alice, 1956-1958 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Syllabi
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1946-1951 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Syllabus and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Spring 1953. Routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Spring 1954. Routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
    Spring 1955. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Spring 1958. Syllabus
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 25-26)
    Spring 1960. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Spring 1962. Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Spring 1963. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 351, 1946-1963 (Box 15, Folder 29-33)
  - Courses - ILR 390, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    Fall 1957. Syllabi
  - Courses - ILR 400, 1947-1960 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 430, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Courses - ILR 430, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 37-38)
    Fall 1964. Syllabi, course handouts, exams, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Courses - ILR 430, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 39-41)
    Fall 1966. Syllabi, course handouts, exams, and routine correspondence